let questions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: "Thor played what video game in Avengers: Endgame",
    answer: "Fornite",
    options: ["GTA", "Fornite", "Minecraft", "COD"],
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: "Scott Lang was trapped in the Quantum Realm for how long?",
    answer: "5 years",
    options: ["6 years", "10 years", "8 years", "5 years"],
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: "What are the names of Wanda’s twins?",
    answer: "Billy and Tommy",
    options: [
      "Lane and Pane",
      "Billy and Tommy.",
      "Harry and Larry",
      "Vol and Billy",
    ],
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: "Who is the firstborn child of Odin?",
    answer: "Hela",
    options: ["Thor", "Loki", "Hela", "Frigga"],
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    question: "What does TVA stand for?",
    answer: "Time Variance Authority",
    options: [
      "Total Valency Auto",
      "Temporary Virtual Authority  ",
      "Time Variety Authority",
      "Time Variance Authority",
    ],
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question: "Who directed Eternals?",
    answer: "Chloé Zhao",
    options: ["Riley Jane", "Chloé Zen", "Chloé Zhao", "Kelly Jane"],
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question: "Stan Lee made his final cameo in which Marvel movie?",
    answer: "Avengers: Endgame",
    options: [
      "Avengers: Infinity War",
      "Avengers: Endgame",
      "Thor: Ragnarok",
      "Captain America: Civil War",
    ],
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question: "Hawkeye has how many children?",
    answer: "Three",
    options: ["Four", "Two", "Five", "Three"],
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question: "What is Tony Stark’s daughter’s name",
    answer: "Morgan Stark",
    options: ["Morgan Stark", "Chloé Stark", "Meghan Stark", "Kelly Stark"],
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question: "Who is the Winter Soldier?",
    answer: "Bucky",
    options: ["Bucky", "Tony", "Harry", "Bruce"],
  },
  {
    number: 11,
    question: "Thor’s Mjolnir is made from the metal of a dying ____?",
    answer: "Star",
    options: ["Star", "Planet", "God", "Black Hole"],
  },
  {
    number: 12,
    question: "Pym Particles were created by who?",
    answer: "Hank Pym",
    options: ["Hank Pym", "Henry Pym", "Harry Pym", "Het Pym"],
  },
];
